

SHAILY GANDHI

UX/UI designer

CONTACT

shailymgandhi@gmail.com

shaily.design

in linkedin.com/in/shaily-gandhi

+31 6 84480755

SKILLS

UX design
UI design
Prototyping and Wireframing
Problem solving
User research
User interviews & testing

TOOLS

Figma / Sketch / Miro / Adobe XD / Photoshop / AutoCAD / ARCHICAD / Revit / Google Sketchup / Invision

EDUCATION

UX/UI Bootcamp Ironhack, Amsterdam 2021 - Current

Bachelors of Architecture CEPT University, Ahmedabad 2007 - 2013

Student Exchange Program TUM, Munich. 2011

PROFILE

I find the underlying concepts of Architecture & UX design very similar - from research to documentation to team dynamics and construction.

My approach to architecture has already been very grounded in user research and focused on human experience rather than just building an environment.

I am a designer, dedicated to work towards achieving goals and to carefully create products that bring positive change into people's lives.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Designer

April 2018 - October 2020

KENK Architecten B.V., Amsterdam

- Worked on various large scale projects, including luxury apartments with commercial spaces, student housing, multi-family housing, housing for the refugees.
- Worked on all the design process which includes working from preliminary design phase, building permit drawings to the construction drawings.
- A great experience learning about the Users from Dutch housing market.

Associate Architect

Keystone Architects, Bangalore

Noved several smarkstate residential, commercial & hospitality projects

- As part of the design team, met clients & discussed the creative & analytical design process
- Prepared detailed drawings & managed site execution for several projects
- Analysed cost & benefits of the projects

Junior Architect

footprints E.A.R.T.H., Ahmedabad

October 2013 - September 2014

- · Worked on various design, competition projects
- Model-making

